<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Features on Shabash</title><link>https://info.shabashkids.online/features/</link><description>Recent content in Features on Shabash</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 00:02:53 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://info.shabashkids.online/features/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Safety &amp; Privacy</title><link>https://info.shabashkids.online/features/safety/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://info.shabashkids.online/features/safety/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="your-familys-safety-is-our-top-priority"&gt;Your Family&amp;rsquo;s Safety is Our Top Priority&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At Shabash, we believe that a tool for families must be built on a foundation of trust. Because we are parents ourselves, we&amp;rsquo;ve designed Shabash with the same level of security and privacy we demand for our own children.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="privacy-by-design"&gt;Privacy by Design&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unlike many other apps, Shabash is not built on data collection. We have a very simple philosophy: &lt;strong&gt;Your data belongs to you.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Family Chore Tracking</title><link>https://info.shabashkids.online/features/chores/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://info.shabashkids.online/features/chores/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="keep-everyone-on-task"&gt;Keep Everyone on Task&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shabash makes chore management collaborative. Parents and children can view the same list of tasks and check them off as they are completed. With clear schedules and flexible assignment options, daily routines become easier to manage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="key-highlights"&gt;Key Highlights&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Assign to any family member&lt;/strong&gt; – choose who should be responsible for each chore.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Editable by both parents&lt;/strong&gt; – families can add or modify chores together.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mark as complete&lt;/strong&gt; with one tap from the dashboard.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id="how-it-works"&gt;How It Works&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Parents or kids both can creates a new chore with title, description, emoji, and star value.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Select a frequency and who it&amp;rsquo;s assigned to.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Child sees the chore on their dashboard and marks it done when finished.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Parents approve and stars are added to the kid&amp;rsquo;s balance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chores can be paused or archived when they are no longer needed, keeping the list clean and focused.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Stars &amp; Rewards</title><link>https://info.shabashkids.online/features/rewards/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://info.shabashkids.online/features/rewards/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="reward-good-work"&gt;Reward Good Work&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Turning chores into a game keeps kids motivated. With Shabash, every completed task earns stars that can be spent on rewards chosen by the family. This positive reinforcement encourages responsibility and makes household chores enjoyable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="rewards-workflow"&gt;Rewards Workflow&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Parents set up rewards&lt;/strong&gt; with a title, cost and optional expiration or limit.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kids browse the store&lt;/strong&gt; to see what they can earn and plan their efforts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Claiming an item&lt;/strong&gt; triggers an optional approval step for parents.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stars are deducted&lt;/strong&gt; only after approval to keep balances accurate.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Badges and achievements appear automatically when children hit milestones, providing extra encouragement and a sense of accomplishment.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>